Guide to the Cornell University College of Veterinary Medicine Subject Files and Photographs, 1888-2004
Cornell University College of Veterinary Medicine Subject Files and Photographs, 1888-2004
- Series XII. Programs and Conferences
  - Two rows of foreign delegates on steps of Willard Straight Hall visiting Cornell after the 12th International Veterinary Congress, in New York City, August 19, 1934, 1934 (Box 46, Folder 49)
  - Six photos of International Veterinary Congress, London, 1949, includes Dean WA Hagan, 1949 (Box 46, Folder 49)
  - Large group of men and women in front of door of building with blinds; Daniel Salmon and Sesco Stewart in front row -- could be an AVMA meeting, Undated (Box 46, Folder 46)
  - Korean Visit, 1998 (Box 46, Folder 47)
  - Senator Hillary Clinton arriving by black limousine outside College entrance, 2006-03-06 (Box 46, Folder 48)
  - Senator Clinton walking into the Hagan Room, 2006-03-06 (Box 46, Folder 48)
  - Senator Hillary Clinton in profile with Dr. Rodney Page, Alfonso Torres, Dean Donald Smith and President Hunter Rawlings, 2006-03-06 (Box 46, Folder 48)
  - Dean Donald Smith at lectern with Dr. Rodney Page, Senator Clinton, President Hunter Rawlings and Dr. Robert MacKenzie, 2006-03-06 (Box 46, Folder 48)
  - Dean Donald Smith at lectern with Dr. Rodney Page and Senator Clinton, 2006-03-06 (Box 46, Folder 48)
  - Senator Hillary Clinton speaking, 2006-03-06 (Box 46, Folder 48)
  - Audience in attendance at visit of Senator Clinton, 2006-03-06 (Box 46, Folder 48)
  - Senator Hillary Clinton (profile) with Dean Donald Smith, 2006-03-06 (Box 46, Folder 48)
    Item number: UP 186-06-21
  - Senator Hillary Clinton receiving gift from Dean Donald Smith, 2006-03-06 (Box 46, Folder 48)
    Item number: UP 186-06-17
  - Senator Hillary Clinton with Dr. Alfonso Torres, 2006-03-06 (Box 46, Folder 48)
    Item number: UP 186-06-06
  - Senator Hillary Clinton with Dean Donald Smith and Mrs. Doris Smith, 2006-03-06 (Box 46, Folder 48)
    Item number: UP 186-06-02
  - Senator Hillary Clinton with Carol Merkur, 2006-03-06 (Box 46, Folder 48)
    Item number: UP 186-06-14
  - Three rows of men in suits beside Moore Lab; not Southern Tier VMA, could be Bureau of Animal Industry veterinarians of New York State; Includes Professors Donald W Baker, Myron G Fincher, Dean William A Hagan, DH Udall, Grant Sherman Hopkins., 1949 (Box 46, Folder 52)
    Item number: 4654
  - Eight men in suits standing, one pointing to another; Dr. Stephen Roberts (right); Taken by photographer in Puerto Rico, 1955 (Box 46, Folder 52)
  - Two rows of men kneeling and standing outside near sheds; includes Dean WA Hagan, SJ Roberts, FH Fox, 1946 (Box 46, Folder 52)
  - Row of men standing outside in front of a barn; Veranus A. Moore (left) with cane; Dr DH Udall? (4th from left with cane), Undated (Box 46, Folder 52)
  - Meeting of presidents, deans and directors of the New York State Colleges with officers of the State University, May 24, 1949, 1949 (Box 46, Folder 52)
  - Two rows of men in suits seated and standing; Ontario Veterinary College, visit of AVMA Council on Education inspectors, April 1950, 1950 (Box 46, Folder 52)
  - Cornell group on board SS Empress of France onroute to Stockholm, July 1953; includes Drs. Hadley Stephenson, Myron G Fincher, Dean William A Hagan, 1953 (Box 46, Folder 52)
  - Head table of 15 men in suits at a banquest with other people dining at tables in frontand floral draperies in back; Seated include: Dr. PP Levine, Dr. Myron G Fincher, Dean William Hagan; standing: Dr. Peter Olafson, Undated (Box 46, Folder 52)
  - Two rows of men in suits at head table with empty dining tables in front and picture frame in back; includes: Dr. PP Levine, Dean William A Hagan, Dr. Peter Olafson, Dr. Myron G. Fincher., Undated (Box 46, Folder 52)
  - Two rows of 7 men in suits in front of leaf pattern curtain, 1952 (Box 46, Folder 52)
    Item number: 6179-B
  - Two rows of men and women standing and seated in front of a speckled curtain; Dr. Lennart Krook (4th from right, standing), 1973 (Box 46, Folder 52)
    Item number: 4325-1
  - Four rows of men in suits kneeling and standing with two lantern lights on wall behind; Dr George Poppensiek (seated, 2nd row, 2nd from left), Undated (Box 46, Folder 52)
    Item number: 882A1048-23
  - Large group of men and women in coats outside in front of steel girder structure with lighting and tanks, Undated (Box 46, Folder 52)
  - Group of 20 men and women in coats outside in front of steel girder structure with lighting and tanks, Undated (Box 46, Folder 52)
  - Group photo taken in Centennial Room: includes Donald Smith, Katherin Edmondson, Bruce Calnek, Mary Ellen Calnek, Richard Grambow, Jerry Belinski, Pat Janhonen, Rodney Page, Robert Gilmour, Robert Gilbert, about late 1990s, Undated (Box 46, Folder 52)
  - Black tie event: with Dean Donald Smith and Mrs. Doris Smith, Undated (Box 46, Folder 46)
  - Veterinary Advisory Committee, 1949 (Box 46, Folder 50)
    Item number: #4-3633
  - SAB Advisory Committee, Fort Detrick, 1956 (Box 46, Folder 50)
  - Equine advisory council in front of James Law Auditorium; Dean Edward C Melby (left); Dr. Douglas Antczak (3rd from left); Dr. Stephen Roberts (4th from left), 1980 (Box 46, Folder 50)
  - Alumni meeting 1968: seated at table (l to r): Dr GC Poppensiek, Dr SJ Roberts, DR Wc "Bud" Trecher, Dr. L Field, Dr. Leo Wuori, Dr Hadley Stephenson, Dr Deke DeCamp, 1968 (Box 46, Folder 31)
  - Alumni meeting 1968: 1st row (l to r) Dr Deke DeCamp, Dr Hadley Stephenson, Dr George Poppensiek, ??; 2nd row (l to r) Dr Lincoln Field, Dr Leo Wuori, Dr. Bob Buffald?, Dr Stephen Roberts, ???, 1968 (Box 46, Folder 31)
  - VRT Dedication 1974: President Dale Corson speaker with other speakers on platform, 1974 (Box 46, Folder 51)
    Item number: 74-5-27-11
  - VRT Dedication 1974: President Dale R Corson, 1974 (Box 46, Folder 51)
    Item number: 74-5-27-12
  - VRT Dedication 1974: speaker, Dr. George Poppensiek, 1974 (Box 46, Folder 51)
    Item number: 74-5-27-14
  - VRT Dedication 1974: speaker, 1974 (Box 46, Folder 51)
    Item number: 74-5-27-15
  - VRT Dedication 1974: speaker with other speakers on platform, 1974 (Box 46, Folder 51)
    Item number: 74-5-27-19
  - VRT Dedication 1974: speaker, 1974 (Box 46, Folder 51)
    Item number: 74-5-27-21
  - VRT Dedication 1974: speaker, 1974 (Box 46, Folder 51)
    Item number: 74-5-27-24
  - VRT Dedication 1974: speaker, 1974 (Box 46, Folder 51)
    Item number: 74-5-27-27
  - VRT Dedication 1974: Dean George C Poppensiek speaking, 1974 (Box 46, Folder 51)
    Item number: 74-5-27-30
  - VRT Dedication 1974: speaker, 1974 (Box 46, Folder 51)
    Item number: 74-5-27-31
  - VRT Dedication 1974; facing Schurman Hall library wing with guests on left, back corner of platform on right, 1974 (Box 46, Folder 51)
    Item number: 74-5-27-37
  - VRT Dedication; Dean George Poppensiek speaking from platform with 5 speakers seated behind, 1974 (Box 46, Folder 51)
    Item number: 74-5-27-51
  - VRT Dedication 1974: Dr. Dorsey W Bruner, Dr James Gillespie, 1974 (Box 46, Folder 51)
    Item number: 74-5-27-54
  - VRT Dedication 1974: 3 guests, 1974 (Box 46, Folder 51)
    Item number: 74-5-27-58
  - VRT Dedication 1974: 3 guests, Dr. Jack Geary, 1974 (Box 46, Folder 51)
    Item number: 74-5-27-61
  - VRT Dedication 1974: Dr A Gordon Danks, guest, 1974 (Box 46, Folder 51)
    Item number: 74-5-27-62
  - VRT Dedication 1974: 2 guests, 1974 (Box 46, Folder 51)
    Item number: 74-5-27-63
  - VRT Dedication 1974; facing Library wing of Schurman Hall with guests seated on left and platform on right; evergreen shrubs in foreground, 1974 (Box 46, Folder 51)
    Item number: 74-5-27-65
  - VRT Dedication 1974: speaker, speaker, Dr George Poppensiek, President Dale Corson, 1974 (Box 46, Folder 51)
    Item number: 74-5-27-70
  - VRT Dedication 1974: President Dale Corson, speaker, 1974 (Box 46, Folder 51)
    Item number: 74-5-27-74
  - VRT Dedication 1974: speaker, Dr. George Poppensiek, President Dale Corson, speaker, 1974 (Box 46, Folder 51)
    Item number: 74-5-27-77
  - VRT Dedication 1974: guest, guest, Dr. George Poppensiek, 1974 (Box 46, Folder 51)
    Item number: 74-5-27-78
  - VRT Dedication 1974: Dr. George Poppeniek, Dr. Harry M. Glass, speaker, 1974 (Box 46, Folder 51)
    Item number: 74-5-27-80
  - VRT Dedication 1974: President Dale Corson, guest, 1974 (Box 46, Folder 51)
    Item number: 74-5-27-84
  - VRT Dedication 1974: 4 guest, Dr. Donald Postle, 1974 (Box 46, Folder 51)
    Item number: 74-5-27-85
  - VRT Dedication 1974: Mrs. Nellie Corson, President Dale Corson, guest, 1974 (Box 46, Folder 51)
    Item number: 74-5-27-88
  - VRT Dedication 1974: speaker, guest, Mrs Edith Poppensiek, guest, 1974 (Box 46, Folder 51)
    Item number: 74-5-27-90
  - VRT Dedication 1974: guest, guest, President Dale Corson, guest, 1974 (Box 46, Folder 51)
    Item number: 74-5-27-92
  - VRT Dedication 1974: 4 guests, 1974 (Box 46, Folder 51)
    Item number: 74-5-27-95
  - VRT Dedication 1974: 4 guests, 1974 (Box 46, Folder 51)
    Item number: 74-5-27-96
  - VRT Dedication 1974: speaker, guest, Mrs. Edith Poppensiek, guest, 1974 (Box 46, Folder 51)
    Item number: 74-5-27-97
  - VRT Dedication 1974: Dr Dorsey W Bruner, Dr. James A Baker, guest, 1974 (Box 46, Folder 51)
    Item number: 74-5-27-98
  - VRT Dedication 1974: Dr Ellis P Leonard, Mrs Edith Poppensiek, speaker, guest, 1974 (Box 46, Folder 51)
    Item number: 74-5-27-100
  - VRT Dedication 1974: Dr George Poppensiek, guest, 1974 (Box 46, Folder 51)
    Item number: 74-5-27-102
  - VRT Dedication 1974: guest, Mrs Edith Poppeniek, Dr Julius Fabricant, 1974 (Box 46, Folder 51)
    Item number: 74-5-27-105
  - VRT Dedication 1974: Dr. George Poppeniek, speaker, Dr. James Gillespie, 1974 (Box 46, Folder 51)
    Item number: 74-5-27-107
  - VRT Dedication 1974: Dr George Poppensiek, speaker, Dr. James Gillespie, 1974 (Box 46, Folder 51)
    Item number: 74-5-27-108
  - VRT Dedication 1974: Dr. George Poppensiek, guest, Dr. James Gillespie, 1974 (Box 46, Folder 51)
    Item number: 74-5-27-109
  - VRT Dedication 1974: Five guests, 1974 (Box 46, Folder 51)
  - VRT Dedication 1974: Three women with Dr Donald Postle (right), 1974 (Box 46, Folder 51)
    Item number: 74-5-27-112
  - VRT Dedication 1974: Dr A Gordon Danks (left), 1974 (Box 46, Folder 51)
    Item number: 74-5-27-114
  - VRT Dedication 1974; showing numerous rows of seated guests in front of Schurman Hall and the James Law Auditorium, 1974 (Box 46, Folder 51)
    Item number: 740615-1-27A
  - Faculty: Katherine Edmondson, Linda Mizer, Alexander deLahunta, Howard Evans, John Hermanson, 2005 (Box 46, Folder 60)
  - Faculty: Susan Suarez, Linda Mizer, Alexander deLahunta, Howard Evans, John Hermanson, 2005 (Box 46, Folder 60)
  - Faculty: John Hermanson, Bonni Voiland, Alexander deLahunta, Kathy Earnest-Koons, 2005 (Box 46, Folder 60)
  - Deans: Donald F Smith standing with Robert O. Gilbert, 2005 (Box 46, Folder 60)
  - Dean: Donald F Smith speaking with attendees in background, 2005 (Box 46, Folder 60)
  - Dean Donald Smith standing with female student (left), 2005 (Box 46, Folder 60)
  - Dean Donald Smith standing with female student, Dana LeVine? (right), 2005 (Box 46, Folder 60)
  - Dean Donald Smith leading procession with white "V" banner behind next to Olin Library, 2005 (Box 46, Folder 60)
  - Student carrying banner next to stone wall of Schoelkopf Field, 2005 (Box 46, Folder 60)
  - "College of Veterinary Medicine" banner in procession, 2005 (Box 46, Folder 60)
  - "College of Veterinary Medicine" banner and white "V" in procession near Weill Hall, 2005 (Box 46, Folder 60)
  - Dean Donald Smith and Mrs Doris Smith (pink jacket) with female student carrying bouquet, 2005 (Box 46, Folder 60)
  - Students and family in stands at commencement, 2005 (Box 46, Folder 60)
  - Veterinary faculty-student picnic at Stewart Park - students unpacking food bags, 1935 (Box 46, Folder 53)
  - Veterinary faculty-student picnic at Stewart Park - eating at table, 1935 (Box 46, Folder 53)
  - Veterinary faculty-student picnic at Stewart Park - standing near benches: Dean William Hagan, Drs Herbert Gilman, Brunett, Cameron, 1935 (Box 46, Folder 53)
  - Veterinary faculty-student picnic at Stewart Park - 3 sitting on bench: Goss, Barker, Sunderville, 1935 (Box 46, Folder 53)
  - Veterinary faculty-student picnic at Stewart Park - playing horseshoes, 1935 (Box 46, Folder 53)
  - Farm and Home Week. Dr. AnthonySylstra in poultry disease laboratory demonstrating poultry necropsy, 1947 (Box 46, Folder 54)
    Item number: 544.1947?
  - Farm and Home Week exhibit on examining animal parasites, Undated (Box 46, Folder 54)
  - Farm and Home Week. Visitor looks into microscope at exhibiton anaplasmosis in cattle, Undated (Box 46, Folder 54)
  - SCAVMA Honor Day - first annual dinner for seniors in Willard Straight Hall, 1940 (Box 46, Folder 55)
    Item number: 510.194
  - SCAVMA Honor Day - 2 rows of student prize winners seated and standing in Straight Hall, 1952 (Box 46, Folder 55)
  - Honor Day - 5 seated and standing: EJ Hoff, JR McAuliff, JE Croshaw Jr, AR Greenwood, WK Loomis, Undated (Box 46, Folder 55)
  - Dedication of Dykstra Hospital at Kansas State University, includes Carl Bvradnly, General Elmer Young, President McCain, General Wayne Kester, Dean Red Leasure, 1955 (Box 46, Folder 56)
  - Four men standing in front of charcoal portraits, one with heavy glasses, Undated (Box 46, Folder 56)
  - Ten men and women seated at a draped head table with large mirror behind. Dean William and Mrs Hagan at far right, Undated (Box 46, Folder 56)
  - Eight men and women seated at round table in Latin Quarter, Sept 1955; Dr. Ellis P Leonard (standing 2nd from right), 1955-09-14 (Box 46, Folder 56)
  - Three men seated; l to r: ER Cushing, Louis Corwin, Alexander Zeissig, 1945 (Box 46, Folder 56)
    Item number: 201
  - Red ribbon cutting: Dean Donald Smith, Alfonso Torres, and guest, Undated (Box 46, Folder 52)
  - Students and public near microscopes, 1974 (Box 46, Folder 57)
    Item number: 740420-1-20
  - Students in anatomy lab with dog skeleton and 3 children, 1974 (Box 46, Folder 57)
    Item number: 740420-1-16
  - Public standing around wire enclosure with Beagle dogs, 1974 (Box 46, Folder 57)
    Item number: 74-4-2-1-4
  - Students and public grouped around horse's head and hay sack, 1975 (Box 46, Folder 57)
    Item number: 750423-1-8
  - Students and public with sheep eating hay, 1975 (Box 46, Folder 57)
    Item number: 750423-2-24
  - Student shining flashlight into fistulated cow in view of public, 1975 (Box 46, Folder 57)
    Item number: 750423-1-4
  - Dark-haired girl rubbing head of light-colored horse in stanchion, 1975 (Box 46, Folder 57)
    Item number: 750423-1-34
  - Blonde haired girl rubbin head of dark horse in stanchion, 1975 (Box 46, Folder 57)
    Item number: 78-41--2-16
  - Child rubbind head of goat held by student, 1978 (Box 46, Folder 57)
    Item number: 780410-1-15
  - Dark-haired woman feeding grain to Holstein cow, 1980 (Box 46, Folder 57)
    Item number: 80-15-3
  - Two children touch ducklings in tank, 1980 (Box 46, Folder 57)
    Item number: 80-5-9
  - Children watch ducklings slide down ramp, 1980 (Box 46, Folder 57)
    Item number: 800407-1-7A
  - Public watches Corgi dog retrieving spools in breezeway, 1980 (Box 46, Folder 57)
    Item number: 800407-3-36
  - Row of men and bows in stetson hats, 1982 (Box 46, Folder 57)
    Item number: 12A
  - Child with fingers in mouth looking a baby chicks, 1982 (Box 46, Folder 57)
    Item number: R1-2A
  - Students holding mouth of fish open, 1983 (Box 46, Folder 57)
    Item number: A30408-2-30
  - Girl looking at skeleton of a cat, 1983 (Box 46, Folder 57)
    Item number: A30408-2-18
  - Student explaining radiographs to child, 1983 (Box 46, Folder 57)
    Item number: 830408-4-4
  - Children and adults looking at rows of horses teeth mounted on a board, 1985 (Box 46, Folder 57)
  - Elderly woman in wheelchair rubbing a calico cat, 1985 (Box 46, Folder 57)
    Item number: PR4-13-85
  - Bitch dog with puppies from first successful artificial insemination from semen transported internationally by Dr Ellis P Leonard, 1955 (Box 46, Folder 59)
    Item number: 801.1
  - Technician holding puppies with bitch from first successul artificial insemination from semen transported internationally by Dr Ellis P Leonard, 1955 (Box 46, Folder 59)
    Item number: 810.11
  - Row of five puppies from first successul artificial insemination from semen transported internationally by Dr Ellis P Leonard, 1955 (Box 46, Folder 59)
    Item number: 810.12
  - Terrier Day 1980 held at Equine Research Park, 1980 (Box 46, Folder 58)
  - College exhibit at New York State Fair, fall 1921 by Dr Benner on diseases of cattle breeding and equine disease demonstration, 1921 (Box 46, Folder 61)
  - College exhibit at New York State Fair Sept 1923, 1923 (Box 46, Folder 61)
  - College exhibit at New York State Fair, Sept 1924 with calf in pen probably by a committee to demonstrate diseases of calves and parasitic diseases of all species, 1924 (Box 46, Folder 61)
  - College exhibit at New York State Fair, Sept 1924 with crate of chickens, 1924 (Box 46, Folder 61)
  - College exhibit at New York State Fair, 1928 with crate of chickens by Dr Earl Brunett, 1928 (Box 46, Folder 61)
  - College exhibit at New York State Fair, 1918, with flags hanging from ceiling by Dr. Earl Sunderville, 1918 (Box 46, Folder 61)
  - College exhibit at New York State Fair, nd, life cycle of poultry parasites, Undated (Box 46, Folder 61)
  - Horseshoeing table. "Teaching - horseshoeing", Undated (Box 46, Folder 62)
    Item number: 612-1
  - Veterinarian Exhibit - US Army Veterinary Unit on horseback in city street. "Army - Veterinary Unit, U.S. Army", Undated (Box 46, Folder 62)
    Item number: 612-2
  - Dr Hadley Stephenson (left) and Dr Howard Milks (right) bandage broken leg of greyhound dog. "Practice - Is there another fracture?", Undated (Box 46, Folder 62)
    Item number: 612-3
  - Veterinarian examining chicken held by farmer. Practice - Looking for the trouble", Undated (Box 46, Folder 62)
    Item number: 612-4
  - Dr Myron Fincher with students Johnson, and Hopinsted in field with cow. "Teaching - Students helping in an emergency on the farm.", Undated (Box 46, Folder 62)
    Item number: 612-5
  - Veterinarians gathered at annual conference. "Annual Conference - Extension of service to alumni and practitioners.", Undated (Box 46, Folder 62)
    Item number: 612-6
  - Dr Denny H Udall examing udder of a cow. "Dairy Inspection - Determining fitness for milk production.", Undated (Box 46, Folder 62)
    Item number: 612-7
  - Meat inspectors. "Meat Insection - Insuring a safe meat supply.", Undated (Box 46, Folder 62)
    Item number: 612-8
  - Dr BJ Errington doing dentistry on a large horse. "Practice - Dentistry.", Undated (Box 46, Folder 62)
    Item number: 612-9
  - Dr Herbert Gilman (left) and Dr. Cameron in research laboratory. "Research - Exact laboratory methods.", Undated (Box 46, Folder 62)
    Item number: 612-10
  - Dr Donald W Baker (left seated) collecting data from sheep in indoor pen. "Research - Taking notes in the field.", Undated (Box 46, Folder 62)
    Item number: 612-11
  - Mr Henry Kriesel, 2nd year student, assisting in physiology putting chicken in a chamber. "Teaching Physiology - Student learning about metabolism.", Undated (Box 46, Folder 62)
    Item number: 612-12
  - Veterinarian examining pig held by farmer in field. "Practice - Saving future process taxpayers.", Undated (Box 46, Folder 62)
    Item number: 612-13
  - Student with microscopes in lab. "Teaching - Long hours of careful application.", Undated (Box 46, Folder 62)
    Item number: 612-14
  - Dr Howard J Milks (center) with 1935 students with surgical cases. "Teaching - Operative cases, surgical clinic.", Undated (Box 46, Folder 62)
    Item number: 613-15
  - Dr Walter L Williams dissecting a specimen. "Research - Careful dissections are necessary.", Undated (Box 46, Folder 62)
    Item number: 612-16
  - Dr Earl Sunderville dissecting a cow carcass. "Teaching - Anatomy from a preserved specimen.", Undated (Box 46, Folder 62)
    Item number: 612-17
  - Veterinarian Exhibit - Poster "Training and Activities of the Veterinarian", Undated (Box 46, Folder 62)
    Item number: 612-18
  - Pathology Department residents outside in rows, June 1981, 1981 (Box 47, Folder 32)
  - Pathology Department residents and faculty outside in rows, June 1981, 1981 (Box 47, Folder 32)
  - Pathology Department residents and faculty, June 1987, 1987 (Box 47, Folder 32)
  - CVM departmental and unit group photos taken in 2000 for the millenium, 2000 (Box 47)
  - US Army Meat and Dairy Hygiene School, Quartermaster Depot, 45th class, 1945-1946, Undated (Box 47, Folder 33)
  - US Army Medical Field Service School, at Hoff Hall in Pennsylvania, 1946, Undated (Box 47, Folder 33)
  - Eighteen veterinary students being sworn in as Army 1st Lieutenants at Cornell ROTC unit, 1943, Undated (Box 47, Folder 33)
  - Five rows of students in khakis beside Barton Hall; Prof Myron Fincher in dark suit in center 2nd row, Undated (Box 47, Folder 33)
  - 10 rows of veterinary corpsmen in khaki uniforms with pointed building behind and flag with "3206 Company C", Undated (Box 47, Folder 33)
  - US Army Veterinary Corps inspecting meat, Undated (Box 47, Folder 33)
    Item number: 611
  - US Army Veterinary Corps on horseback in formation on a city street, Undated (Box 47, Folder 33)
    Item number: 610
  - US Army Veterinary Corps 7 men gathered around table of meat samples, Undated (Box 47, Folder 33)
  - US Army Veterinary Corps 2 men inspecting beef carcass, Undated (Box 47, Folder 33)
    Item number: CO-1086
  - US Army Veterinary Corps 2 men in surgical masks tattooing a monkey after a TB test, Undated (Box 47, Folder 33)
    Item number: CO-1476
  - US Army Veterinary Corps 2 men examining a Beagle dog, Undated (Box 47, Folder 33)
    Item number: CO-701
  - Faculty and staff of the Veterinary College by department or unit taken at the 2000 millenium, 2000 (Box 47, Folder 35)
  - Dr, WA Hagan (2nd from right) inspecting sheep dipping at Fort Sam Houston,Texas, 1953 (Box 47, Folder 34)
  - Dr WA Hagan (left) with Maj Gen Martin Commandant of 1953 ROTC camp at Fort Sam Houston, Texas, 1953 (Box 47, Folder 34)
  - Dr WA Hagan (right) with President of Union Stock Yards in San Antonio, Texas, 1953 (Box 47, Folder 34)
  - Dr WA Hagan (3rd from left) with 3 cadets and pack mule at Fort Sam Houston, Texas, 1953 (Box 47, Folder 34)
  - Dr W A Hagan (2nd from left) talking with 4 others at Fort Sam Houston, Texas, 1953 (Box 47, Folder 34)
  - Dr W A Hagan has lunch with the veterinary cadets from Cornell at Fort Sam Houston, Texas, 1953 (Box 47, Folder 34)
- Series XIII. Graphics and Audiovisual Material
  - Postcards featuring the College (Box 21)
  - Wearers of the "C" photo album (Vet students who participated in sports), 1902-1939 (Box 14)
  - Wearers of the "C" photo album Vet students who participated in sports), 1940-1961 (Box 14)
  - Posters (Box 9)
  - Franklin Loew Memorial Display, 2004 (Box 9)
  - Deans Hagan and Poppensiek Caricature (in pastels), ca. 1960s (Box 9)
  - Place Cards for Honor Day - Caricature of the Faculty, by Vincent Paciello, 1940 (Box 16)
  - Place Cards for Honor Day - Animals, by Rebecca Gifford, 1940 (Box 17)
  - Pages and loose photos from Edwin R. Jackson's scrapbook, ca. 1915 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Glass plate negatives of college buildings, equipment and activity, including two large negatives of students, faculty, and James Law gathered for a lesson in equine surgery., ca. 1910 (Box 22)